Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- Sports Illustrated: 1954: Name, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 12)
- Sports Illustrated: 1954: Sample Columns and Stories (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 13)
- Sports Illustrated: 1957: Edi:t Format Change (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 14)
- Sports Illustrated: 1977: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 15)
- Sports Illustrated: 1978: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 16)
- Sports Illustrated: 1979: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 17)
- Sports Illustrated: 1980: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 18)
- Sports Illustrated: 1981: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 19)
- Sports Illustrated: 1982: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 20)
- Sports Illustrated: 1983: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 21)
- Sports Illustrated: 1984: The Year in Sports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 22)
- Sports Illustrated: 1985: Letters, Reports (Offsite-box 3982, Folder 23-24)
- Sports Illustrated: 1985: Letters, Reports (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 1)
- Sports Illustrated: 1986: Publishing Dodge Truck "Pop-Up" Ad (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 2)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising Convention (April), 1954 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 13)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising: Miscellaneous, 1954 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 14)
- Sports Illustrated: Anniversary (1st), 1955 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 15)
- Sports Illustrated: Anniversary (5th), 1959 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 16)
- Sports Illustrated: Anniversary (10th), 1961, 1964 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 17)
- Sports Illustrated: Anniversary (20th), 1974 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 18)
- Sports Illustrated: Anniversary (25th), 1979 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 19-20)
- Sports Illustrated: Anniversary (25th), 1979 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 2)
- Sports Illustrated: Awards, 1956, 1960 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 21)
- Sports Illustrated: Awards, 1955-1959, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 3)
- Sports Illustrated: Awards, 1957 (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Books, 1958 (Offsite-box 3981, Folder 22)
- Sports Illustrated: Exhibit Images Panel #2, 1937 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated: Imitations, 1958-1959, 1965, 1976, 1991 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 3)
- Sports Illustrated: Imitations, 1981 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 5)
- Sports Illustrated: Legal, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated: Letters Department, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 5)
- Sports Illustrated: Old Sports Illustrated, 1936-1938, 1949 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Advertising and Promotion, 1954 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Circulation, 1954 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 8)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Dry Runs, 1954 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Dummies, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4038, Folder 10-11)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Dummies, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4039, Folder 1-2)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Type and Logo Experiments, 1954 (Offsite-box 4039, Folder 3)
- Sports Illustrated: Pre-Publication: Miscellaneous, 1954 (Offsite-box 4039, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated: Publicity Files, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4039, Folder 5-7)
- Sports Illustrated: Survey and Studies, 1972 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Survey and Studies, 1974 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Survey and Studies: Subscribers' Attitude to Sports Illustrated (SI), 1974 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 8)
- Sports Illustrated: Venture: Women's Sports and Fitness, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 9)
- Spot Television, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 4080)
- Spot Television, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 4081)
- Spot Television, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 4081)
- Syndication, 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 10)
- Syndication: Sample Columns, 1936-1939 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 11)
- Syndication: Test Copy, 1965 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 12)
- Syndication, International: Africa, 1959 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 13)
- Syndication, International: Australia, 1940-1949, 1954, 1959, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 14)
- Syndication, International: Britain, 1963 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 15)
- Syndication, International: Colombia, 1963 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 16)
- Syndication, International: France, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 17)
- Syndication, International: Germany, 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 18)
- Syndication, International: Greece, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 19)
- Syndication, International: India, 1961 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 20)
- Syndication, International: Italy, 1954, 1960 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 21)
- Syndication, International: Japan, 1965 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 22)
- Syndication, International: Latin America: Marcha del Tiempo Sample Copies, 1941 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 23)
- Syndication, International: Latin America: Miscellaneous, 1940-1943, 1959 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 24)
- Syndication, International: South Africa, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 25)
- Syndication, International: Sweden, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 26)
- Temple-Eastex, 1954-1961, 1979 (Offsite-box 4039, Folder 8-9)
- Temple-Eastex, 1954-1961, 1979 (Offsite-box 4040, Folder 1)
- Tide Magazine Copies Set #2, 1927-1931 (Offsite-box 3983, Folder 272)
- Time Advertising Record, 1956-1979 (Offsite-box 4080)
- Time: Advertising: Rediscover America Campaign, 1991 (Offsite-box 4040, Folder 2)
  1 videocassette (VHS) (65 min.): On container: "Rediscover America: 75th Anniversary of America's National Parks"
  1 audio cassette tapes: On label: "Rediscover America Vol. 1"
  1 audio cassette tapes: On label: "Rediscover America Vol. 2"
- Time: Awards, 1942-1976 (Offsite-box 4040, Folder 5-6)
- Time: Advertising: Promotion 1969 Power of Print II, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 1)
- Time: Anniversary 1938 (15th): Circulation: Promotion (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 2)
- Time: Anniversary 1938 (15th): Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 3)
- Time: Anniversary 1943 (20th): Blurbs (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 4)
- Time: Anniversary 1943 (20th): Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 5)
- Time: Anniversary 1943 (20th): Staff Dinner (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 6)
- Time: Anniversary 1943 (20th): Staff Dinner Speeches (Audio Tapes) 3/11/43 (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 7)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Anniversary Dinner 3/3/43 Eric Hodgins introduces R.E. Larsen, beginning of Larsen speech"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Anniversary Dinner 3/3/43 end of Larsen speech, Hodgins introduces Luce, Luce speech"
- Time: Anniversary 1943 (20th): Veteran Subscribers (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 8)
- Time: Anniversary 1948 (25th): Blurbs (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 9)
- Time: Anniversary 1948 (25th): Circulation (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 10)
- Time: Anniversary 1948 (25th): Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 11)
- Time: Anniversary 1948 (25th): Story of an Experiment (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Anniversary 1953 (30th): Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 14)
- Time: Anniversary 1953 (30th): Original Subscribers, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 15)
- Time: Anniversary 1958 (35th) (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 16)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Auer Party (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 17)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Bios, A-G (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 18)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Bios, H-Z (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 19-20)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Bios, Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 21)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Correspondence (Offsite-box 3984, Folder 22)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner Invitations, Menu, Seating, Etc. (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 1)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Linen Party (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 2)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Lists (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 3-5)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 6-7)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Publicity (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 8)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Speeches (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 9)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Cover Dinner: Time Story (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 10-11)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 12)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Staff Dinner: Invitation, Menu, Seating, Etc. (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 13)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Staff Dinner: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 14)
- Time: Anniversary 1963 (40th): Staff Dinner: Speeches (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 15)
- Time: Anniversary 1968 (45th): (Never Took Place), 1967 (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 16)
- Time: Anniversary 1973 (50th) Film Proposal (Never Took Place), 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 17)
- Time: Anniversary 1973 (50th) Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3985, Folder 18)
- Time: Anniversary 1973 (50th): Staff Dinner (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 1)
- Time: Anniversary 1983 (60th) (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 2)
- Time: Anniversary (60th), 1983 (Offsite-box 4040, Folder 3)
- Time: Anniversary (60th) Cover Dinner Guest List (Dinner Never Took Place), 1983 (Offsite-box 4040, Folder 4)
- Time: Anniversary 1993 (70th) (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 4)
- Time: Anniversary 1993 (70th): History Photocopies (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 5)
- Time: Anniversary 1998 (75th) (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 6)
- Time: Anniversary 1998 (75th): Cover Dinner (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 7)
- Time: Anniversary 1998 (75th): Publicity (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 8)
- Time: Anniversary 1998 (75th): Video Tape Numbers and Logs (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 9)
- Time: Anniversary 2003 (80th): "80 Days That Changed the World" (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 10)
- Time: Awards, 1941-1942, 1947, 1950-1958, 1962, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 11)
- Time Bicentennial, 1975 (Offsite-box 4008, Folder 2)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Time Bicentennial 6/30/75 – 7/5/75 Sample Reel Show #Two"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Time Bicentennial 6/30/75 – 7/5/75 Sample Reel Show #Four"
- Time Books: Greatest Places of History, 2011 (Offsite-box 4040, Folder 7)
- Time Books: History's Greatest Events, 2011 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 1)
- Time by 16: LibRef: Digital Business Review, 2006 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 9)
- Time, Canada: Advertisers 1943-1973 (Missing 1970 and 1971), 1943-1970 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 12)
- Time, Canada: Issues Samples, 1968-1975 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Renewals 1924-1929 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 15)
- Time: Circulation: Newsstands: Reports, 1950-1961 (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 12)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1969-1971, 1980 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 16)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Perpetual Subscriptions, 1949 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 17)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Sample Pamphlets, 1923-1929 (Offsite-box 3986, Folder 18-19)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Sample Pamphlets 1930-39, 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Sample Pamphlets 1940-49, 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 3)
- Time: Circulation: Promotion: Sample Pamphlets 1950-59 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 4)
- Time: Covers 1938-1948 Odds/End/Poor Quality (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 5)
- Time: Covers 1980 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 6)
- Time: Covers 1981 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 7)
- Time: Covers Weekly Cover Subject Reports, 1974-1983 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 8-10)
- Time: Marked Story Lists 1990 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 11)
- Time: Edit: Marked Story Lists 1991 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 12)
- Time: Edit: Marked Story Lists 1992 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 13)
- Time: Edit: Marked Story Lists 1993 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 14)
- Time: Edit: Marked Story Lists 1994 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 15)
- Time: Edit: Marked Story Lists 1995 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 16)
- Time: Edit: Marked Copy Lists 1996 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 17)
- Time: Edit: Marked Copy Lists 1997 (Offsite-box 3987, Folder 18)
- Time: Edit: Marked Copy Lists 1998 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 1)
- Time: Edit: Marked Copy Lists 1999 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 2)
- Time: Edit: Marked Copy Lists 2000 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 3)
- Time: Edit: Marked Copy Lists 2001 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 4)
- Time: Edit: Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 2)
- Time: Edit: Regional Edits in Time by Stanley Stillman, 1973 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 5)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1946-47, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 6)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 19448, 1948 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 7)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1949 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 8)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1950 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 9)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1951 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 10)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1951 and Before, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 11)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1952 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 12)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1952, 1953 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 13)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1954 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 14)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1955 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 15)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1956 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 16)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1957 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 17)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1958 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 18)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1959 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 19)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1960 (empty) (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 21)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1961 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 22)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1962 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 23)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1963 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 24)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1964 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 25)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1965 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 26)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1966 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 27)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1967 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 28)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1968 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 29)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1969 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 30)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1970 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 31)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1971 (Offsite-box 3988, Folder 32)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1972 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 1)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1973 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 2)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1974 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 3)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1975 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 4)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1976 and 1977, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 5)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1978 and 1979, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 6)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1980 and 1981, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 7)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1982-82, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 8)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 9)
- Time: Edit: Staff Sheets 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 10)
- Time: Edit: Staff Sheets 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 11)
- Time: Edit: Staff Sheets 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 12)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 13)
- Time: Edit: Staff and Contributors Lists 1996 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 14)
- Time: Edit: Staff and Contributors Lists 1997 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 15)
- Time: Edit: Staff and Contributors Lists 1998 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 16)
- Time: Edit: Staff and Contributors Lists 1999 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 17)
- Time: Edit: Staff and Contributors Lists 2000 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 18)
- Time: Edit: Staff Sheets 2001 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 19)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 2002 (Offsite-box 3989, Folder 20)
- Time: Edit: Staff Lists 2003 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 1)
- Time: Edit: Story Development 1939 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 2)
- Time: Edit: Story Development 1955 (Sample Query and Response) (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 3)
- Time: Education Program Miscellaneous, 1966, 1971, 1974, 1988, 1994 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 4)
- Time: Education Program: With Me Tonight Radio Show James Alberse, 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 5)
- Time-Hachette: 1988 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 6)
- Time-Hachette: 1989 January-May (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 7)
- Time-Hachette: 1989 June-December (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 8)
- Time-Hachette: 1990 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 9)
- Time-Hachette: 1991 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 10)
- Time-Hachette: Bank Loans and Financing, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 11)
- Time-Hachette: Elle Korea, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 12)
- Time-Hachette: Elle Korea [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Offsite-box R84)
- Time-Hachette: Elle pour Homme, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 13)
- Time-Hachette: Elle Japon: Business Plans, 1989 (Offsite-box 3990, Folder 14)
- Time-Hachette: Elle Japon: Financial Info, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 1-2)
- Time-Hachette: Elle Japon: Status Reports, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 3)
- Time-Hachette: Elle Deco, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 4)
- Time-Hachette: Employment Agreements [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Offsite-box R84)
- Time-Hachette: Japan, Inc: Joint Venture: Closing Documents [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R84)
- Time-Hachette: Legal 1988 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 4)
- Time-Hachette: Legal 1989 January-February (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 5-6)
- Time-Hachette: Legal 1989 March (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 7-8)
- Time-Hachette: Legal 1989 April- (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 9-11)
- Time-Hachette: Life Japan, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 12-13)
- Time Imitations 1929 and Before, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 14)
- Time: Imitations, 1929, 1980 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 3)
- Time Imitations 1930-34, 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 3991, Folder 15)
- Time: Imitations 1935-39, 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 1)
- Time: Imitations 1940-1949, 1940, 1941, 1946, 1947 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 2)
- Time: Imitations 1950-59, 1950-51 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 3)
- Time: Imitations 1960-69, 1960-64 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 4)
- Time: Imitations 1970-79 (empty), undated (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 5)
- Time: Imitations 1980-89, 1984, 1989 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 6)
- Time: Imitations 1990-99, 1990, 1993 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 7)
- Time Inc. Special Interest Sale Proposal, 2006 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 8)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1953 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 9)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1954 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 10)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1961 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 11)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1962 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 12)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1969 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 13)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1971 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 14)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1972 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 15)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1973 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 16)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1974 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 17)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1975 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 18)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1978 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 19)
- Time Inc. Annual Report 1979 and 1980, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 20)
- Time Inc. Directors Dinner 8/16/78, 1978 (Offsite-box 4008, Folder 3)
  1 audio cassette: On label: "Time Inc. Directors Dinner 8/16/78 Tape Two: Media Discussion"
- Time Inc. Logo Original Art, 1986 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 4)
- Time: Index 1969 (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 21)
- Time International: 1941: Samples/Air Express Edition (and Dummies) (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 22-23)
- Time International: 1942: Issues/Samples (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 24)
- Time International: 1943: Issues/Samples including Pony (Offsite-box 3992, Folder 25-26)
- Time International: 1944: Issues/Samples: Full Size (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 1)
- Time International: 1944: Issues/Samples: Pony (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 2-3)
- Time International: 1945: Issues/Samples: Full Size (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 4)
- Time International: 1945: Issues/Samples: Pony (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 5-7)
- Time International: 1945: Issues/Samples: V-Mail (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 8)
- Time International: 1946: Issues/Samples (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 9)
- Time International: 1947: Issues/Samples (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 10)
- Time International: 1959: Issues Samples: Australia, 1959, 1987 (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 11)
- Time International: 1974: Surveys and Studies: Time Europe (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 12)
- Time International: 1975: Surveys and Studies: Time South Africa (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 13)
- Time International: 1977: Surveys and Studies: Time Australia (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 14)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion Sale Memos 1959 (Offsite-box 3993, Folder 15-16)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion: Sale Memos 1960 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 1-2)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion: Sale Memos 1961 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 3-4)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion: Sale Memos 1962 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 5-7)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion: Sale Memos January-July 1963 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 8-9)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion: Sale Memos August-December 1963 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 10-11)
- Time International: Advertising: Promotion: Sale Memos January-March 1964 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 12)
- Time International: Letters Reports (incomplete), 1990 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 13)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1966: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 14)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1967: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 15)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1969: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 16)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1970: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 17)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 18)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 19)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: 1981: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 20)
- Time International: Marketing: Promotion Pieces: Undated Materials Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 21)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1946: Latin America (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 22)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1947: Latin America (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 23)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1948: Canada, 1947 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 24)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1951: Canada (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 25)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1952: Canada (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 26)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1952: Latin America (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 27)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1954: Canada (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 1)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1956: Canada (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 2)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1956: Latin America (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 3)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1957: Latin America 1957 "Survey of Business in…" etc (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 4)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1958: Atlantic Subscriber and Newsstand Studies (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 5)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1958: Latin America 1958 "Census of Business In…" (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 6)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1959: Canada Subscriber Study (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 7)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1960: Latin America Argentina and Venezuela (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 8)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1961: Atlantic Sweden and Switzerland (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 9)
- Time International: Marketing: Surveys and Studies: 1961: Latin America (Offsite-box 3994, Folder 10)